[Music]
focus ID
innovate image ICICI Lombard and CNBC
tv18 present India risk management
Awards a very good evening ladies and
gentlemen I'm Reza Madadi from network
18 and I'd like to extend a very warm
welcome to all of you at the 6th edition
of ICICI Lombard general insurance and
CNBC tv18 present India risk management
award a one of its kind initiative by
ICICI Lombard general insurance and CNBC
tv18 to recognize those organizations
that have created and adopted
world-class risk management practices
over the last five years this has become
the most coveted platform for
recognizing India's best risk management
teams and tonight we are here to
felicitate the winners of season six and
for this first set of awards that also
like to invite the earth market our
elite group CFO and group CIO at Manila
and Mahindra to please join the
presenter
the first set of awards this year is for
best risk management framework and
systems they recognize the initiatives
taken by a company to build a
comprehensive risk management framework
to mitigate macro-level
company-wide risks our first award
category this evening is best risk
management framework and systems
emerging Indian companies and the winner
is the winner is cpp Group
[Music]
[Applause]
our company embarked on this journey a
few years back and today to be
felicitated with this award is a real
honor we are a company which receives
data from various organizations and in
today's world where data is key and it's
the oil
we've put systems together we're in you
know whether it's our call center or
digitally wherever the data is stored
we've put systems that once the data
comes to our company whether it's the
digital drive or the individual drive
every individual every system in our
company is a risk manager and now let's
find out who the second winner of the
category is the winner is dr. love pat
labs
[Applause]
[Music]
being in healthcare this is very
important where we keep a lot of data
which is related to personal health care
of the patients and customers so for us
data protection which is very very
important and which we are protecting so
we are spending a lot of you know
initiative in terms of IT digital's to
protect the data from the outside
perspective we have lot of you know IT
enabled software's which protect the
data from that suppose somebody can hack
your data
somebody can you know that is a lot of
system we have deployed in in our
company alright moving on to our next
award category this evening best risk
management framework and systems IT ITES
let's take a look at the winner the
winner is Genpact limited
[Applause]
[Music]
the risk management system and Genpact
is actually more like an integrated
framework we embarked on this journey
about three years back earlier it was a
traditional approach to risk management
being handled by different functions now
it's more like an integrated framework
across all our locations across the
different verticals industries that we
service and it's actually embedded more
like in our DNA across levels in the
organization be it starting from the
goals we set for each of our senior
leadership to deliver on to actually the
way we actually do our work through
managing risks through a proactive risk
management system internally flagging of
risks regularly and figuring out
mitigation plans and monitoring them
across our next award category tonight
is for best risk management framework in
systems in sustainability
and the winner is the winner is Shree
Cement limited
[Music]
[Applause]
we are delighted to win this award
in fact we at SRI cement believe
business is not only about making money
but D risking yourselves and we have
been working on this since long and this
is the first time that we have received
this award so obviously the whole team
is very delighted and we are thankful
for CNBC and ICICI Lombard for
recognizing the efforts of the company
and giving us this award we believe risk
mitigation goes a long way increasing
the sustainability of the company moving
on to the next category of the India
risk management awards 2020 this one is
best risk management framework in
systems FMCG and the winner is
the winner is Tata global beverages
Limited
[Music]
[Applause]
it's been an absolute privilege and
honor to receive the India risk
management award for the best risk
management framework and systems for
FMCG under FMCG category thank you to
CNBC and the jurors for giving this
prestigious award at Tata global
beverages we believe that the core
tenants of risk management philosophy of
this philosophy that I'm talking about
has been you know how do we manage mid
to long-term risks or risks that could
impact the mid to long-term growth
objectives of the business right now
therefore it is very imperative that the
risk management process is integrated to
the mid term planning process or the
strategy setting process of the
organization and for the next set of
awards I'd like to invite on stage
Ramaswamy Nathan Head of Corporate
Centre larsen and toubro
to please join us here on stage
well our fifth award category this
evening is best risk management
framework and systems telecom and the
award goes to
[Music]
the winner is Reliance Geo Infocom
Limited
[Applause]
liquid and it's a motivation for my team
and as well as for the recognition of
the hard work do it so we just started a
journey and almost a year back but I
feel it's like a good stimulus for us to
work better and more harder to achieve
of new heights for the function we have
a multiple risk management systems to be
with we are a CP heavy company so a CP
GRC the governor the scan compliance
tool has been implemented so that's for
the for the framework and the system's
part but in addition to that we are also
using multiple cutting-edge analytics
tool as well as the dashboarding systems
from tableau and all so the it's quite a
telecom being a very heavy on the
automation side so are always the
endeavour has been to be on sort of
beyond the latest tools and technologies
available in the market and embrace them
in our risk management work and now for
our next category best risk management
framework and systems auto and salami
goes to the winner is
see at limited
[Applause]
[Music]
it's feels great okay a word always
motivates people okay and normally risk
management is not you're not fully
understood or appreciated and the
importance of it is realized only when
something goes wrong okay so we feel
proud to receive this award and we are
delighted we have robust this Chi
identification process it's very
detailed and lots of people reading
various functions are involved in
identification of risks not only we have
good identification process but we also
have a robust risk mitigation process
okay which we regularly monitor at the
management committee level at the
operational team level and board also
reviews it twice a year so that's what I
would say is that a governance that we
have in which sets apart see it from
maybe some of the other companies moving
on to our next award category this
evening best risk management framework
in systems metals and mining and this
award goes to
the winner is Tata Steel Limited
[Music]
could we have been actually wearing the
water I think for five years now and
always feels good to win an award I
think it's a vindication of the effort
you put in put in and what you delivered
as a company so it seems great a Tata
Steel we have been very clear from day
one that it is a business process for us
it is not a compliance process or it is
not a process to be done by a team
sitting somewhere it has to be
implemented by business and I think what
really distinguishes our effort is that
it is so deeply embedded in the business
that it is actually run by the business
as the CRO I'm the facilitator and me
and my team essentially ask questions
push business but the process is run by
business and it is an integral part of
business and decision-making which I
think makes it very special ICICI
Lombard and CNBC tv18 % India Risk
Management Awards ICICI Lombard general
insurance and CNBC tv18 present India
risk management Awards and tonight we
are here to felicitate the winners of
season six all right up next is the
category best risk management framework
in systems power
and the award in this one goes to the
winner is the Tata Power Company Limited
[Applause]
[Music]
shut up about over the last several
years has put in very strong and the
worst system we have a separate
dedicated dedicated risk magazine fans
on their very strong oversight from
office management CFO as well as we have
a board is my main committee which meets
several time in a year to review this
the risk management has such is embedded
into our day-to-day business function
itself then there is a second line also
which reviews it and then as a third
line of defense a internal audit checks
into each and every aspects of the so
for us family the risk which are
emerging on the sustainability side as
the climate change related concerns are
emerging we have put in a lot of
investment in setting up to bring our
plants to beat all the norms it maybe
even exceed those norms and they're
investing heavily on the renewable sites
so other this which are emerging and
also we are investing heavily on the
renewables other this which are emerging
is on the cyber site again we are
prepared for that for the next set of
forwards are also like to invite on
stage rui Bastos cio of Reliance
Industries to join the presenters
all right then let's move on to our next
reward category this evening best risk
management framework and systems
business continuity and this award goes
to
the winner is tart her consultancy
services limited
[Music]
we have made significant investment in
building internal systems which
digitizes this process into end and the
entire system has been deployed globally
across the organization across all
business units and I believe that is
giving us the results and we are very
pleased with that the way I look at it
it is indeed a great validation of the
kind of systems processes and framework
we have deployed in TCS across the
organization which is helping all our
customers in enabling continuous
delivery of critical services even in
case of a disruptive in Surrey moving on
to our next category at the India Risk
Management Awards 2020 best risk
management framework and systems cyber
security and the winner is
the winner is wns Global Services
Private Limited
[Music]
[Applause]
I feel absolutely proud on behalf of the
information security team and every
employer wns to receive this coveted
award and thanks to CNBC and to the
ICICI Lombard and the jury for basically
recognizing us for our initiatives that
we have taken in the field of cyber
security the initiatives that we've
taken in the last year itself
include active threat hunting processes
putting in place a artificial
intelligent system that aids our
security monitoring processes and
massively improving the procedures in
our security operation center well up
next is the award category best risk
management framework and systems risk
governance and the jury had a tough task
selecting the winner for this one so
after much deliberation they decided to
give it to two companies yes we have two
winners this year in this category so
let's in an alphabetical order take a
look at the first winner the winner is
ashok leyland limited
[Music]
[Applause]
fundamentally ashok leyland has always
had a very strong risk management
culture and we have adopted the ISO
31000 as also the co so erm framework
but risk management as the way of life
has been DTOs for ashok leyland
limitation so let's take a look at the
second one now the winner is the Tata
Power Company Limited
[Music]
[Applause]
for the next set of awards I'd like to
welcome on stage weapons irelia cro visa
south asia to please come here and join
the presenter and our next award
category for the evening is best risk
management framework and systems
technology and let's find out who the
winner is the winner is Larsen & Toubro
limited
[Applause]
[Music]
the recognition has been growing over
the last five seven years in terms of
how risk management has been perceived
so from a only which started as a
governance framework some years back
covers now the strategic tactical and
operational risks and it's been a very
exciting journey and a lot of you we are
now people also are wanting to be a part
of a group so it's pretty exciting we
have a risk framework from a3 for
portfolio for three four perspectives
one is at a strategic level which would
typically looking at portfolio geography
and what services you do where you do
how you do all of that a framework and
then the tactical and operational risk
framework is also there with that with a
governance framework we also implemented
system and today most of the projects
where we work on insights most of them
would be connected or connected through
risk systems and it's been a massive
effort over the last two three years and
I guess we will see the benefits of the
reduction of volatility in our
performance for a long period of time
and also protect the company from
unforeseen issues which can come and
mitigate the risk which come along the
way
moving on the next one is best with
management framework and systems PSU
and the winner is
the winner is ONGC bodacious limited
[Music]
[Applause]
well it's very soothing and very
motivating for the team which is which
works very hard to ensure that risk is
properly mapped in the organization
poeple mitigation measures are being
adopted so for the team I feel extremely
happy as a leader of the team we were
the early adopters of the risk
management in terms of identification of
the risk and the mitigation strategies
way back in 2012 and from then on today
we have ISO 3102 2019 this management
system in place which has been ingrained
in all our processes so all the key
executives on the desktops have a SAP
based system which gives us a profile of
risk across all our assets in terms of
heat perhaps in terms of the ongoing
risk emerging rest and enables the
decision-making in an effective manner
and it's time for the final two awards
of the night and for these I'm going to
invite our jury members back on stage
Ramaswamy Nathan Andrew abastos please
join us up here our next award category
is best risk management framework and
systems private company and the winner
is the winner is a short Leyland limited
[Applause]
[Music]
and it's time to announce the final
award off the evening and the category
is threat risk management framework
encryptions the winner is Larsen and
Toubro limited
[Applause]
[Music]
and I'm going to invite all the winners
of tonight to please come up here for a
group photo opportunity the defining
memory of this year's India risk
management Awards
[Music]
ICICI Lombard and CNBC tv18 present
India risk management Awards focus
innovate in the